{
    "questions": [
	{
                "id": "1",
                "question": "Which shape has exactly 5 rectangular faces?",
                "option1": "Pentagonal Prism",
                "option2": "Cuboid",
                "option3": "Octahedron",
                "option4": "Sphere", 

                "Correctans":"Pentagonal Prism"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "2",
                "question": "IS 4 a factor of 28?",
                "option1": "Sometimes",
                "option2": "Yes",
                "option3": "Maybe",
                "option4": "No",  

                "Correctans":"Yes"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "3",
                "question": "Which of these is a quadrilateral?",
                "option1": "Hexagonal Prism",
                "option2": "Semicircle",
                "option3": "Parallelogram",
                "option4": "Pentagon",  

                "Correctans":"Parallelogram"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "4",
                "question": "Which of these is a prime number?",
                "option1": "15",
                "option2": "16",
                "option3": "17",
                "option4": "18",  

                "Correctans":"17"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "5",
                "question": "10 to the power of 4 =",
                "option1": "10000",
                "option2": ".0001",
                "option3": "100000",
                "option4": "1",  

                "Correctans":"10000"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "6",
                "question": "What is the square root of 225 ?",
                "option1": "13",
                "option2": "25",
                "option3": "19",
                "option4": "15",  

                "Correctans":"15"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "7",
                "question": "25% of 1008",
                "option1": "39",
                "option2": "205",
                "option3": "252",
                "option4": "2000",  

                "Correctans":"252"
        },    	   	     
        {
                "id": "8",
                "question": "Pythagoras' theoram will always work in which type of triangle?",
                "option1": "isosceles",
                "option2": "right angled",
                "option3": "scalene",
                "option4": "equilateral",  

                "Correctans":"right angled"
        },    	   
        {
                "id": "9",
                "question": "What is the name for a straight line from the centre to the edge of a circle?",
                "option1": "chord",
                "option2": "circumference",
                "option3": "diameter",
                "option4": "radius",  

                "Correctans":"radius"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "10",
                "question": "The predecessor of the smallest 5-digit number is?",
                "option1": "9999",
                "option2": "99999",
                "option3": "10001",
                "option4": "100001",  

                "Correctans":"9999"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "11",
                "question": "19/6 is a number between?",
                "option1": "2 and 3",
                "option2": "3 and 4",
                "option3": "19 and 20",
                "option4": "6 and 18",  

                "Correctans":"3 and 4"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "12",
                "question": "3 hrs 40 mins equals",
                "option1": "120 mins",
                "option2": "180 mins",
                "option3": "220 mins",
                "option4": "240 mins",  

                "Correctans":"220 mins"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "13",
                "question": "The smallest 4-digit number formed by using the digits 0, 3, 5, 6 is?",
                "option1": "0356",
                "option2": "6530",
                "option3": "6035",
                "option4": "3056",  

                "Correctans":"3056"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "14",
                "question": "Solve 8/n = 12/9",
                "option1": "n=96/9",
                "option2": "n=9",
                "option3": "n=6",
                "option4": "n=5",  

                "Correctans":"n=6"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "15",
                "question": "Evalute the expression 75 - (-z) - |-51| when z = -3",
                "option1": "27",
                "option2": "21",
                "option3": "23",
                "option4": "129",  

                "Correctans":"21"
        }, 
         {
                "id": "16",
                "question": "If x,y and z are consecutive positive integers, with x<y<z and x+y+z an even number, which of the following could be the value of z?",
                "option1": "1",
                "option2": "2",
                "option3": "4",
                "option4": "5",  

                "Correctans":"5"
        },    	   	     
         {
                "id": "17",
                "question": "If sum of three different prime numbers is an even number, what is the smallest of the three?",
                "option1": "2",
                "option2": "3",
                "option3": "5",
                "option4": "7",  

                "Correctans":"2"
        },    	   	     
         {
                "id": "18",
                "question": "If n is an even number, all of the following must be even except?",
                "option1": "n",
                "option2": "2n",
                "option3": "2n+n",
                "option4": "2n+5",  

                "Correctans":"2n+5"
        },    	   	     
         {
                "id": "19",
                "question": "On a number line what is the distance between -3 and 7?",
                "option1": "10",
                "option2": "8",
                "option3": "7",
                "option4": "5",  

                "Correctans":"10"
        },    	   	     
         {
                "id": "20",
                "question": "Find the average of the first five prime numbers.",
                "option1": "5.6",
                "option2": "5.9",
                "option3": "6",
                "option4": "6.3",  

                "Correctans":"5.6"
        }]
}